Igor Polajžer

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Igor.polajzer@student.um.si

+386 70 495 374

LinkedIn profile

DESCRIPTION

I am Igor Polajžer, a dedicated 21-year-old student pursuing a degree in Computer Science at the Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (FERI) in Maribor. Currently in my third and also last year of studies, I exhibit a strong work ethic and a relentless drive to acquire new skills and experiences within the tech industry.

EDUCATION

September 2018 – June 2022

Technic of mechatronics,

Electrical and Computer School Ptuj / Ptuj

In progress (2 semesters left)

dipl. eng. computer science and informatics (BSc),

The Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Computer / Maribor

LAGNUAGES

Slovenian, native

English, fluent

German, basic

EXPERIENCE

August 2023 – October 2023

 ${\bf Internship-software\ engineer}\ Skylabs\ d.o.o$

At Skylabs d.o.o, I was responsible for transforming C++ libraries into Pythoncompatible modules by creating wrappers. Additionally, I developed a RESTful API to provide easy access to these libraries. My role involved the entire development lifecycle, from concept to deployment. Through this experience, I enhanced my skills in C++, Python, web development and project management gaining valuable expertise in software integration and API design

August 2024 – currently working part-time

Internship - QA engineer Setronica d.o.o

At Setronica, I was responsible for the quality assurance of LLM models. My role involved thoroughly reviewing the output material generated by these models, assessing the accuracy of their solutions, and labeling them as either acceptable or in need of improvement. In addition to grading the outputs, I provided detailed comments that highlighted specific inaccuracies and offered constructive feedback to help improve the model's performance.

SKILLS

C	HTML	SQL
C++	CSS	Jetpack Compose
C#	JavaScript	Android Studio
Java	Node.js	git/github
Kotlin	Web stacks (MERN, LAMP)	docker